Ajay
that I want to purchase a good health insurance policy for my family
and when I search or survey to purchase the policy then it comes to know
that today there are 10 general
insurance companies and 5 health
insurance companies that deal in health insurance.
Now the question arises that which will be the
best health
insurance policy for me and my family. Friends,
you will get the answer to this question very easily in today's video
because Live Minute has made this work very easy for you
and I have
shared with you their settings available in Subscribe. So
hi friends my name is Deepak Jain and Power
Infinitive Forms and
friends now if we want to check a good health insurance
policy then we always
see that at such a time when we
need that health insurance of the plant
then we do not have any kind of problem
subscribe of our city so let's start
about the top 15 health insurance plans
so first of all I will give you the basic
understanding of this whole thing which is in front of you in this first of all about the
patient i.e.  There is a
need to stay in the hospital for 24 hours,
that is called in-question hospitalization.
You have been given the rating of real post graduation, that is, the expenses
before admission in the hospital and the expenses after discharge are
called post graduation. No
claim bonus means the period in which there is
no claim and after that the bonus
which increases or is received in the year of no claim bonus,
now its rating is
restoration benefit here, that is, we
can assume it like this that as soon as the time of injury is
over, the
refill which is left after the injury gets recharged again,
this is called restoration benefits,
from its rating here is non-
medical expense, this cover which
is not medical related expenses, like we
can assume picket or gloves, these types of
expenses, if we consider the pension limit, that is,
what kind of tapping, what kind of
expansion ratings are there in the product,
how many types of experiences are there in the product
Inside now the cutting of the overall product is the
search for complaints points above half the fuel surcharge, that is,
within how much time so many claims are settled,
track record of that,
here we
will discuss about the company, about the company's product and about the overall rating and
discuss about the premium quality, so let me tell you here that
if you look at it, it means
score, in the portability rating in the premier,
where you will see a higher rating,
it means that the product is a bit
expensive, so in the worst position here is
Money Plant Signal's Profile
Prime Advantage Plan and its overall
rating is f4
986, its premium affordability rating is
4.0, ICICI Lombard's
Complete Health Insurance Health Selva,
its overall rating is 4984 and
premium acidity rating points is
on the third position, lemon juice and its overall
rating is 3.0,
companies and its overall rating point type is
S and premium quality rating
comes on the third position, Aditya Birla Health's
Active Ashva Plan and  Its rating is
4.5 Star and premium quality
rating is
Magma hd1 health plan and its rating is
4.5 Let's
talk about
Profession Lakir
Vighna
and
Amazing
We will talk about this
Subscribe and
Subscribe
3.5 Star Plus Aditya Birla Health's
Active Help Platinum Premier Plan and
its product rating is the overall
rating and some other and premium
quality rating is
50 Next let's talk about
Remedy Pratima Restore and its overall
rating is and
Amazing
Reliance General's Ghyan Power Plant and
its
star rating is 3.5 Star Zoom
Subscribe
and Medium Let's
talk about
Remedy Pratima Secure and its rating is
4.2 overall rating and its
premium affordability rating is A It is
at the potent position that Digit's Health
Insurance Comfort Plan and its overall
rating is 4.2 and premium
affordability rating
is at the 315 position Edelweiss General
Insurance Company's Family Health
Insurance Gold Plan and its overall
rating is 4.1 and premium affordability
rating is A3
Softsystems  And this video will be helpful to you
if you are selecting
a good health insurance plan for yourself or your family.
If you liked this video, then
please do like it. If you have any
question, then
you can coordinate with our team by commenting in the comment box.
If you liked this video, then do share the
video with your friends and relatives. I am
convinced
but not the least, you must subscribe to this channel.
Friends, if you
want to make a career in the field of insurance or want to buy a health insurance policy for yourself or your family,
then you can
please coordinate with our team on the number written in the description.
So friends, thank you, thank you so
much for watching the video. Thank you too.